Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - A
        - Area 51 - Aqua funk; Crossfade, 1999; SR-10793; Area 51 (Box 173)
          Catalog # PROMO 26; A-side Matrix # 12PROMO-26PA1
          Promo Recordings
          Tipton, United Kingdom
        - Area Code: 305 - Brand new groove, 1982; SR-10794; Area Code: 305 (Box 173)
          Catalog # DD 6002; A-side Matrix # DD 6002A
          Dash
        - Arkarna - House on fire (Disc one), 1997; SR-10795; Arkarna (Box 173)
          In same jacket as # SR-10796. Double album
          Catalog # 0-43878; A-side Matrix # 0-43878-A
          Kinetic Records
        - Arkarna - House on fire (Disc two), 1997; SR-10796; Arkarna (Box 173)
          In same jacket as # SR-10795. Double album
        - Arketipo - Kaliope, 1990; SR-10797; Arketipo (Box 173)
          Catalog # OUT 3388; A-side Matrix # OUT 3388 A
          Out
        - Armada - Le life style dans l'abstract, 1997; SR-10798; Armada (Box 173)
          Catalog # GREED 007; A-side Matrix # GREED 007-A1
          9mm Records
        - Arman-E - Summer lover, 1990; SR-10799; Arman-E (Box 173)
          In same jacket as # SR-10800. 2 copies
          Catalog # WAR-086; A-side Matrix # WAR086A
        - Arman-E - Summer lover, 1990; SR-10800; Arman-E (Box 173)
          In same jacket as # SR-10799. 2 copies
        - Armareda - Come better (than that), 2000; SR-10801; Armareda (Box 173)
          Catalog # EAS 15163; A-side Matrix # XSS-15163A-1B
        - Armatrading, Joan - (I love it when you) call me names; Drop the pilot, 1983; SR-10802; Armatrading, Joan (Box 173)
          Catalog # SP-17229; A-side Matrix # A&M SPO17229A(RE-1)-ESI
        - Armband - I need; Dame amor, 1983; SR-10803; Armband (Box 173)
          Catalog # I.P.S. 002; A-side Matrix # IPS 002 A
          I.P.S. Records
        - Armenta - I wanna be with you, 1983; SR-10804; Armenta (Box 173)
          Catalog # SF 201 P; A-side Matrix # SF-201-A
          Savoir Faire Records
        - Armstrong, Vanessa Bell - Something inside so strong, 1989; SR-10805; Armstrong, Vanessa Bell (Box 173)
          Catalog # 1245-1-JDAA; A-side Matrix # 1245-1-JD-AAA
          Jive
        - Army Of Lovers - Crucified; Ride the bullet, 1992; SR-10806; Army Of Lovers (Box 173)
          Catalog # 0-40351; A-side Matrix # 0-40351-A SR1
          Giant Records
          Nashville, Tennessee
        - Arpadys - Arpadys, 1977; SR-10807; Arpadys (Box 173)
          Catalog # 2933 802; A-side Matrix # POL 2933 802 1 380 CIDIS
          Polydor
        - Arpeggio - Breakout, 1979; SR-10808; Arpeggio (Box 173)
          Catalog # PD D-515; A-side Matrix # PDD515A-2
        - Arpeggio - Let the music play…, 1978; SR-10809; Arpeggio (Box 173)
          Catalog # PD-1-6180; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6180-AS
        - Arpeggio - Breakout, 1980; SR-10810; Arpeggio (Box 173)
          Catalog # PD-1-6230; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6230-AS-K
        - Arrested Development - Africa's inside me, 1994; SR-10811; Arrested Development (Box 173)
          In same jacket as # SR-10812. 2 copies
          Catalog # Y-58309; A-side Matrix # Y58309-A1-REI
          Chrysalis
        - Arrested Development - Africa's inside me, 1994; SR-10812; Arrested Development (Box 173)
          In same jacket as # SR-10811. 2 copies
        - Arrested Development - People everday, 1992; SR-10813; Arrested Development (Box 173)
          Catalog # 12cool265; A-side Matrix # 12 COOL 266 A-01-01-1
          Cooltempo
        - Arrested Development - United front, 1994; SR-10814; Arrested Development (Box 173)
          Catalog # Y-58199; A-side Matrix # Y-58199-A-1
        - Arrington, Charisse - Down with this, 1996; SR-10815; Arrington, Charisse (Box 173)
          Catalog # MCA8P-3769; A-side Matrix # MCA12609
        - Arrington, Charisse - Wind me up; Ain't no way, 1996; SR-10816; Arrington, Charisse (Box 173)
          Catalog # MCA8P; A-side Matrix # MCA 12741
        - Arrington, Steve - Dancin' in the key of life, 1985; SR-10817; Arrington, Steve (Box 173)
          Catalog # A 9534; A-side Matrix # A9534 TE A
        - Arrington, Steve - Nobody can be you, 1983; SR-10818; Arrington, Steve (Box 173)
          In same jacket as # SR-10819. Different discs
          Catalog # DMD 606; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-44206-2
        - Arrington, Steve - I, 1983; SR-10819; Arrington, Steve; Steve Arrington's Hall of Fame (Box 173)
          In same jacket as # SR-10818. Different discs
          Catalog # 80049-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-835140-C
        - Arrington, Steve - Feel so real, 1985; SR-10820; Arrington, Steve (Box 173)
          Catalog # DMD 816; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-47454-1
        - Arrington, Steve - Weak at the knees, 1983; SR-10821; Arrington, Steve; Steve Arrington's Hall of Fame (Box 173)
          Catalog # DMD 630; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-44233-1
        - Arrington, Steve - Turn up the love, 1985; SR-10822; Arrington, Steve (Box 173)
          Catalog # DMD 889; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-48532-1
        - Arrington, Steve - Dancin' in the key of life, 1985; SR-10823; Arrington, Steve (Box 173)
          Catalog # DMD 855; A-side Matrix # STDM-48004-1
        - Arrington, Steve - Stone love, 1987; SR-10824; Arrington, Steve (Box 173)
          Catalog # V-56073; A-side Matrix # V-1-56073-ZZ
          Manhattan Records
        - Arrington, Steve - Lost and found (you can find me present), 1988; SR-10825; Arrington, Steve (Box 173)
          In same jacket as # SR-10826. 2 copies
          Catalog # NR 5001; A-side Matrix # L-11382-NR-5001A-RE
          Nubian Records
        - Arrington, Steve - Lost and found (you can find me present), 1988; SR-10826; Arrington, Steve (Box 173)
          In same jacket as # SR-10825. 2 copies
        - Arrington, Steve - Way out, 1982; SR-10827; Arrington, Steve; Steve Arrington's Hall of Fame (Box 173)
          In same jacket as # SR-10828. 2 copies
          Catalog # KNR-7491-B.U.; A-side Matrix # KNR 7491-A
          Konglather Records
        - Arrington, Steve - Way out, 1982; SR-10828; Arrington, Steve; Steve Arrington's Hall of Fame (Box 173)
          In same jacket as # SR-10827. 2 copies
        - Arrington, Steve - Hall of fame #1, 2004; SR-10829; Arrington, Steve (Box 173)
          Catalog # HP-060; A-side Matrix # HP-60 A
          House Party
        - Arrington, Steve - Homeboy, 1986; SR-10830; Arrington, Steve (Box 173)
          Catalog # DMD 949; A-side Matrix # ST-DM49726-1
        - Arrington, Steve - Summertime lovin'; Special effects from Mars, 1980; SR-10831; Arrington, Steve; Levan, Larry (Box 173)
          Catalog # SG 332; A-side Matrix # SG-332-A
          Salsoul Records
        - Arrington, Steve - No reason, 1991; SR-10832; Arrington, Steve (Box 173)
          Catalog # RDAB-62173-1; A-side Matrix # 07863-62173-1-A1
        - Arrington, Steve - The jammin' national anthem, 1986; SR-10833; Arrington, Steve (Box 173)
          Catalog # DMD 932; A-side Matrix # STDM49318-3
        - Arrow - Deadly, 1985; SR-10834; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # ARROW025; A-side Matrix # ARROW025A
          Arrow Records
          Barbados
        - Arrow - Soca Dance Party, 1990; SR-10835; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # 539 878-1; A-side Matrix # 162-539-878-1A
        - Arrow - Hot hot hot, 1984; SR-10836; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # 4V9 42701; A-side Matrix # 4V9-42701-A
        - Arrow - Zombie soca, 1991; SR-10839; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # ARROW035; A-side Matrix # ARROW-035-A
        - Arrow - Outrageous, 1993; SR-10840; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # ARROW040; A-side Matrix # ARROW-A
        - Arrow - Ride de riddim, 1996; SR-10841; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # 0045; A-side Matrix # ARROW 0045-A
        - Arrow - Heavy energy, 1986; SR-10842; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # ARROW 028; A-side Matrix # ARROW 028-A
        - Arrow - Instant knockout, 1980; SR-10843; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # CR 017; A-side Matrix # CR-017A
          Charlie's Records
        - Arrow - Hot hot hot, 1982; SR-10844; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # ARROW 019; A-side Matrix # ARROW-019-A1
        - Arrow - Rush hour, 1984; SR-10845; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # BSR-AR-021; A-side Matrix # ARROW 021A
          B's Records
        - Arrow - O'la soca, 1989; SR-10846; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # MLPS 9835; A-side Matrix # MLPS 9835 A DMM
        - Arrow - Knock dem dead, 1987; SR-10847; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # 670.4263-A; A-side Matrix # 670.4263-A
          Rio de Janeiro, Brazil
        - Arrow - Turbulence, 1998; SR-10848; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # 0047; A-side Matrix # ARROW-0047-A
        - Arrow - Limbo calypso, 1990; SR-10849; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # 537 846-1; A-side Matrix # 162-537-846-1-A-SP
        - Arrow - Long time, 1984; SR-10850; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # LDSX 220; A-side Matrix # LDSX 220 A
          Quebec, Canada
        - Arrow - O'la soca, 1989; SR-10851; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # MLPS 7829; A-side Matrix # MLPS 7829A
        - Arrow - Groove master, 1988; SR-10852; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # MLPS 7822; A-side Matrix # MLPS 7822A
        - Arrow - Hot-hot-hot, 1982; SR-10853; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # 151.101; A-side Matrix # 151 101-A
          CNR
        - Arrow - Zombie soca, 1991; SR-10854; Arrow (Box 174)
          Catalog # ARROW 036; A-side Matrix # ARROW-036-A
        - Art of Noise - The seduction of Art of Noise (Disc one), 1999; SR-10855; Art of Noise (Box 174)
          In same jacket as # SR-10856. Double album
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # U8P-1503 A
        - Art of Noise - The seduction of Art of Noise (Disc two), 1999; SR-10856; Art of Noise (Box 174)
          In same jacket as # SR-10855. Double album
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # U8P-1503 C
        - Art of Noise - Kiss, 1988; SR-10857; Art of Noise; Tom Jones (Box 174)
          Catalog # 871 039-1; A-side Matrix # 871-039-1-AS-HRM
          China Records
        - Art of Noise - In visible silence, 1986; SR-10858; Art of Noise (Box 174)
          Catalog # BFV 41528; A-side Matrix # BFV 41528 AS CPI
        - Art of Noise - Peter Gunn, 1986; SR-10859; Art of Noise; Duane Eddy (Box 174)
          Catalog # 4V9 42992; A-side Matrix # 4V9 42992 AS CP2
        - Art of Noise - Untitled, 1987; SR-10860; Art of Noise (Box 174)
          Catalog # VAS-2841; A-side Matrix # VAS 2841 A11
        - Art of Noise - Paranoimia, 1986; SR-10861; Art of Noise; Max Headroom (Box 174)
          Catalog # 4V9 43017; A-side Matrix # 4V9 43017 AX
        - Art of Noise - Legs, 1985; SR-10862; Art of Noise (Box 174)
          Catalog # 4V9 42934; A-side Matrix # 4V9 42934 A CPI
        - Artfull Dodgers - 1 mic then pass, 1999; SR-10863; Artfull Dodgers (Box 174)
          Catalog # SR 0200-2; A-side Matrix # SR-0200-A
          Midwestern Union / Silent Records
          San Fransisco, California
        - Artie the 1 Man Party - A mover la colita, 1995; SR-10864; Artie the 1 Man Party; D.J. Juanito (Box 174)
          Catalog # 72392 78048-1; A-side Matrix # 72392-78048-1 SIDE A
          Groove Nation Records
        - Artists United Against Apartheid - Sun city, 1985; SR-10865; Artists United Against Apartheid (Box 174)
          Catalog # ST-53019; A-side Matrix # ST-1-53019-Z2
        - Artists United Against Apartheid - Let me see your I.D. (Sun city), 1985; SR-10866; Artists United Against Apartheid (Box 174)
          In same jacket as # SR-10867. 2 copies
          Catalog # V-56015; A-side Matrix # V-1-56015-240726E-Z1
        - Artists United Against Apartheid - Let me see your I.D. (Sun city), 1985; SR-10867; Artists United Against Apartheid (Box 174)
          In same jacket as # SR-10866. 2 copies
          Catalog # V-56015; A-side Matrix # V-1-56015-240726E-Z2
        - Arthur, Alice - A natural 10, 1980; SR-10868; Arthur, Alice (Box 174)
          Catalog # JC 36800; A-side Matrix # AL 36800-1B
        - Arx - The shop; Simply Ms. Tony, 1994; SR-10869; Arx; Ms. Tony (Box 174)
          Catalog # SIN3003; A-side Matrix # SRI-3003-WEED SIDE
          Sinical Records
          Baltimore, Maryland
        - Artz & Kraftz - What a feeling, 1990; SR-10870; Artz & Kraftz (Box 174)
          Catalog # MOT-4740; A-side Matrix # MOT-10001-FW2
        - Artz & Kraftz - What a feeling, 1990; SR-10871; Artz & Kraftz (Box 174)
          Catalog # L33-18514; A-side Matrix # MOT9999FW1
          RAS
        - Asampete, Pele - Pele Asampete, 1983; SR-10872; Asampete, Pele (Box 174)
          Catalog # RASLPS 43; A-side Matrix # RAS LPS 043 A
        - Asantè - All about you, 1995; SR-10873; Asantè (Box 174)
          Catalog # 44 78314; A-side Matrix # XSS 78314A-1A
        - Asantè - All about you, 1995; SR-10874; Asantè (Box 174)
          Catalog # 44 78314; A-side Matrix # XSS78314B-1A
        - Asantè - Asantè mode, 1995; SR-10875; Asantè (Box 174)
          Catalog # C 57845; A-side Matrix # AL57845-1A
        - Asantè - Look what you've done, 1995; SR-10876; Asantè (Box 174)
          Catalog # CAS 7526; A-side Matrix # XSS7526B-1A
        - Asantè - Look what you've done, 1995; SR-10877; Asantè (Box 174)
          Catalog # 44 78207; A-side Matrix # XSS78207B-2A
        - Ashanti - Don't let them; Only you (Remix); Focus, 2005; SR-11599; Ashanti (Box 174)
          Catalog # DEFR 16242-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16242 1A
          The INC Records
        - Ashanti - Collectables by Ashanti (Disc one), 2005; SR-10878; Ashanti (Box 174)
          In same jacket as # SR-10879. Double album
          Catalog # DEFF 16471-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-16470-1
        - Ashanti - Collectables by Ashanti (Disc two), 2005; SR-10879; Ashanti (Box 174)
          In same jacket as # SR-10878. Double album
          Catalog # DEFF 16472-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-16470-1
        - Ashanti - Only you; Turn it up, 2004; SR-10880; Ashanti (Box 174)
          Catalog # DEFR 16195-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR 16195-1A
        - Ashanti - Breakup 2 makeup (Remix), 2004; SR-10881; Ashanti; Black Child (Box 174)
          Catalog # DEFR 16017-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16017-1A
        - Ashanti - Something's wrong (Bump n' grind), 1994; SR-10882; Ashanti (Box 174)
          Catalog # 72392 78007-1; A-side Matrix # 72392-78007-1-A
          Scotti Bros. Records
        - Ashanti - Still on it, 2005; SR-10883; Ashanti; Wall, Paul; Method Man (Box 174)
          Catalog # DEFR 16445-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR -16445-1A
        - Ashanti - Rock wit u (Awww baby), 2003; SR-10884; Ashanti (Box 175)
          Catalog # DEFR 15867-1; A-side Matrix # BOOOO540-11-A
          Murder Inc Records
        - Ashanti - Rock wit u (Awww baby), 2003; SR-10885; Ashanti (Box 175)
          Catalog # DEFR 15891-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-15891-1A
        - Ashanti - Concrete rose (Disc one), 2004; SR-10886; Ashanti (Box 175)
          In same jacket as # SR-10887. Double album
          Catalog # B0003409-01; A-side Matrix # B0003409-01-LP1A
        - Ashanti - Concrete rose (Disc two), 2004; SR-10887; Ashanti (Box 175)
          In same jacket as # SR-10886. Double album
          Catalog # B0003409-01; A-side Matrix # B0003409-01-LP2A
        - Ashanti - Collectables by Ashanti (Disc one), 2005; SR-10888; Ashanti (Box 175)
          In same jacket as # SR-10889. Double album
          Catalog # B0005924-01; A-side Matrix # B0005924-01-LP1A
        - Ashanti - Collectables by Ashanti (Disc two), 2005; SR-10889; Ashanti (Box 175)
          In same jacket as # SR-10888. Double album
          Catalog # B0005924-01; A-side Matrix # B0005924-01-LP2A
        - Ashaye - Don't stop 'till you get enough, 1981; SR-10890; Ashaye (Box 175)
          In same jacket as # SR-10891; SR-10892. 2 copies. Annotated
          Catalog # MS-618; A-side Matrix # MS-618A
          Montage Records
        - Ashaye - Don't stop 'till you get enough, 1981; SR-10891; Ashaye (Box 175)
          In same jacket as # SR-10890; SR-10892. 2 copies
          Catalog # MS-618; A-side Matrix # MS-618A-RE-1
        - Ashaye - Don't stop 'till you get enough (Michael Jackson medley), 1983; SR-10892; Ashaye; Jackson, Michael (Box 175)
          In same jacket as # SR-10890; SR-10891. Different disc
          Catalog # 8305; A-side Matrix # 8305A
          Record Shack Records
        - Asher D - Brutality, 1988; SR-10893; Asher D; Daddy Freddy (Box 175)
          Catalog # PRO-7196; A-side Matrix # PRO 7196-A
        - Asher D - Jungle skank, 1995; SR-10894; Asher D; DJ Torch (Box 175)
          Catalog # 977.985-A; A-side Matrix # 977.985-A
          360 Records
        - Asheru - Soon come… (Disc one), 2001; SR-10895; Asheru; Blue Black; Unspoken Heard (Box 175)
          In same jacket as # SR-10896. Double album
          Catalog # SHR-008-LP; A-side Matrix # SHR-008-1A
          Seven Heads
        - Asheru - Soon come… (Disc two), 2001; SR-10896; Asheru; Blue Black; Unspoken Heard (Box 175)
          In same jacket as # SR-10895. Double album
          Catalog # SHR-008-LP; A-side Matrix # SHR-008-1C
        - Ashford & Simpson - Nobody walks in L.A., 1986; SR-10897; Ashford & Simpson (Box 175)
          Catalog # V-15272; A-side Matrix # V-1-15272-100368B-100368A-RE1-Z2
        - Ashford & Simpson - It seems to hang on, 1978; SR-10898; Ashford & Simpson (Box 175)
          Catalog # PRO-A-748; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-748-RR1
        - Ashford & Simpson - Found a cure, 1979; SR-10899; Ashford & Simpson (Box 175)
          Catalog # DWBS 8874; A-side Matrix # DWBS-8814-X1XY-1873-S-M1
        - Ashford & Simpson - Street opera, 1982; SR-10900; Ashford & Simpson (Box 175)
          Catalog # ST-12207; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12207-Z3
        - Ashford & Simpson - Real love1, 1986; SR-10901; Ashford & Simpson (Box 175)
          Catalog # ST-12469; A-side Matrix # ST-2-12469-Z1
        - Ashford & Simpson - A musical affair, 1980; SR-10902; Ashford & Simpson (Box 175)
          Catalog # HS 3458; A-side Matrix # HS 1 3458 WW1 #3
        - Ashford & Simpson - Street corner, 1982; SR-10903; Ashford & Simpson (Box 175)
          Catalog # 8528; A-side Matrix # 8528-98150-Z-2
        - Ashford & Simpson - So so satisfied, 1977; SR-10904; Ashford & Simpson (Box 175)
          Catalog # BS 2992; A-side Matrix # BS-1-2992-LULU1-RE1
        - Ashford & Simpson - Performance (Disc one), 1981; SR-10905; Ashford & Simpson (Box 175)
          In same jacket as # SR-10906. Double album
          Catalog # 2WB 3524; A-side Matrix # 2WB 1 3524 JW2 3
        - Ashford & Simpson - Performance (Disc two), 1981; SR-10906; Ashford & Simpson (Box 175)
          In same jacket as # SR-10905. Double album
          Catalog # 2WB 3524; A-side Matrix # 2WB 3 3524 JW2 2
        - Ashford & Simpson - What becomes of love, 1986; SR-10907; Ashford & Simpson (Box 175)
          Catalog # V-15259; A-side Matrix # V-1-15259-1003
        - Ashford & Simpson - Is it still good to ya, 1978; SR-10908; Ashford & Simpson (Box 175)
          Catalog # BSK-3219; A-side Matrix # BSK-13219-RE1-HW1
        - Ashford & Simpson - Solid, 1984; SR-10909; Ashford & Simpson (Box 175)
          Catalog # ST-12366; A-side Matrix # ST-12366-Z2
        - Ashram House - Eternity, 1989; SR-10910; Ashram House (Box 175)
          Catalog # GEE 12004; A-side Matrix # GEE-12-004-A
          WAU Recordings
        - Ashtrax - Digital reason, 2001; SR-10911; Ashtrax (Box 175)
          Catalog # DVNT46XR; A-side Matrix # DVNT-46-XR-A
          Deviant Records
          Norfolk, United Kingdom
        - Asiatic Force - In your face; Stop actin', 1995; SR-10912; Asiatic Force (Box 175)
          Catalog # BF0103; A-side Matrix # BF-0103-1A
          Beat Force Recordings
        - Asona - Pop highlife band, 1985; SR-10913; Asona (Box 175)
          Catalog # MA2422; A-side Matrix # M2422A
          Makossa International Records
        - Asphalt Jungle - Freakin' time, 1979; SR-10914; Asphalt Jungle (Box 175)
          Catalog # # 65; A-side Matrix # 65A
          TEC Records
          Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
        - Assassin - Serieux Dans Nos Affaires, 2000; SR-10915; Assassin (Box 175)
          Catalog # 7243 8965836 1; A-side Matrix # 07243 896583-6A
          Assasin Productions
        - Assassin - Note mon nom sur ta liste!, 1991; SR-10916; Assassin (Box 175)
          Catalog # 879 977; A-side Matrix # 879 977-1 A
          Remark Records
        - Assassin - L'odyssee suit son cours, 1995; SR-10917; Assassin (Box 175)
          Catalog # 7243 8 92880 6 3; A-side Matrix # 9288063A
        - Assassin - l'homicide voluntaire (Disc two), 1993; SR-10918; Assassin (Box 175)
          Catalog # 7243 8 40393 1 8; A-side Matrix # 403918C1
        - Associates - Sulk, 1982; SR-10919; Associates (Box 175)
          Catalog # 1-23727; A-side Matrix # 1-23727-A
          Sire
        - Associates - Fouth drawer down, 1981; SR-10920; Associates (Box 175)
          Catalog # SITU 2; A-side Matrix # 58373A
          Situation Two
        - Associates - Love hangover; 18 carat love affair, 1982; SR-10921; Associates (Box 175)
          Catalog # PRO-A-1063; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-1063-S
        - Associates - A, 1981; SR-10922; Associates (Box 175)
          Catalog # FICSX 13; A-side Matrix # FICSX 13 A
          Fiction Records
        - Associates - Breakfast, 1984; SR-10923; Associates (Box 175)
          Catalog # 249 219; A-side Matrix # Y2-2ST-A2
          WEA Records
        - Astley, Jon - Put this love to the test, 1988; SR-10924; Astley, Jon (Box 175)
          Catalog # DMD 1240; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-55879-55880-1
        - Astley, Rick - Never gonna give you up, 1987; SR-10925; Astley, Rick (Box 175)
          Catalog # 6748-1-RDCD; A-side Matrix # 6784-1-RD-C
          RCA Victor
        - Astra - Dolci aquae, 1997; SR-10926; Astra (Box 175)
          Catalog # PRG 7093; A-side Matrix # PRG 7093-A
          PRG
        - ASU - Nothing but bass, 2004; SR-10927; ASU (Box 175)
          Catalog # BL 010; A-side Matrix # L-13802M-A BL-010 A
          Unknown
          USA
        - Aswad - Don't turn around, 1988; SR-10928; Aswad (Box 175)
          Catalog # MLPS 7823; A-side Matrix # MLPS-7823-A
        - Aswad - Rebel souls, 1984; SR-10929; Aswad (Box 175)
          Catalog # MLPS 9780; A-side Matrix # MLPS-9780-A
        - Aswad - Beauty's only skin deep, 1989; SR-10930; Aswad (Box 175)
          Catalog # MLPS 7828; A-side Matrix # MLPS 7828 A-2
        - Aswad - Live and direct, 1983; SR-10931; Aswad (Box 175)
          Catalog # IMA 6; A-side Matrix # IMA 6 A-1U-1
        - Aswad - Distant thunder, 1988; SR-10932; Aswad (Box 175)
          Catalog # MLPS 9810; A-side Matrix # MLPS-9810-A
        - Aswad - Crucial tracks, 1989; SR-10933; Aswad (Box 175)
          Catalog # MLPS 9833; A-side Matrix # MLPS-9833-A-DMM
        - ATC - It ain't over, 1990; SR-10934; ATC (Box 175)
          Catalog # V-19714-A; A-side Matrix # V-19714A
          SBK Records
        - A.T.E.E.M. - Yeah, 1992; SR-10935; A.T.E.E.M. (Box 175)
          Catalog # 0-25020; A-side Matrix # 0-25020A
        - Athletic Mic League - Volume one, 2000; SR-10936; Athletic Mic League (Box 175)
          Catalog # PN2001; A-side Matrix # INR 265-1A S-42881
          Lab Technicians Productions
          Ann Arbor, Michigan
        - Athletico Spizz 80 - Do a runner, 1980; SR-10937; Athletico Spizz 80 (Box 175)
          Catalog # SP-4838; A-side Matrix # AMSP04838-A
        - Atiya - Jenny do; Let's live, 1989; SR-10938; Atiya (Box 176)
          Catalog # MO028; A-side Matrix # MD28-A
          MO Records
        - Atkins - Feel it, don't fight it, 1982; SR-10939; Atkins (Box 176)
          Catalog # PRO-A-1022; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-1022-ZCA-1541-V1-5-SH1